I had a pretty simple reason for
joining my spy academy.
My parents' restaurant got destroyed.
I needed to start earning my own way.
Other people had much nobler motivations than me,
so it's no wonder I washed out.
You need to recognize your place.
What if we quit pullin' our punches
and just blow Klaus's whole room up?
Good idea!
During the Pre-Impossible Mission Training
When should we set the bomb?
Well, we'd gotta start by luring him out.
We could tell him we made him dinner,
so he should come to the dining room.
I love it!
Then, we can use that opening to
plant a bomb under his bed!
To be honest, I find it hard to imagine that
being enough to take down the boss.
Maybe, but it'll give us some valuable intel either way.
Nah, I think this'll work!
We just need a big enough kaboom!
A real kablooey!
I'm in!
I wanna make it go kablooey too, yo!
Point of interest, if I may?
There's something nobody is mentioning,
so I suppose I'd better say it myself.
We may need to start worrying about
the manor's structural integrity.
SPY CLASSROOM
FILE: Meadow Sara
Ever since we got here,
we've been attacking Teach daily
to try to make him surrender.
Destruction and explosions have become
an everyday occurrence for us,
and it's getting to the point where the damage to
the manor's is getting too severe to overlook.
To illustrate how bad it's gotten,
one of us got literally crushed last night.
What?!
Apparently, one of the doors fell over
the same way it did just now.
It really hurt...
It's starting to interfere with our day-to-day activities.
I say we should start taking turns repairing the manor
the same way we handle the cleaning.
Mark me as opposed.
We're about to head out on a
death-defying mission, remember?
We don't have time to play handyman.
That's no reason to throw
everything else to the wayside.
Right now, we need to devote every
spare second we have to our training.
We can worry about fixing the place up later.
I bet you just don't want to do any more chores.
Go ahead, believe what you want.
Besides, the place gets fixed up
on its own sometimes.
Klaus probably calls in specialist contractors.
You know, repairmen who specialize in
working with spies or something.
Big Sis Monika was talking nonsense.
The manor definitely gets repaired sometimes,
but I've never seen a single contractor around.
It's the work of a ghost.
I'm sure of it.
What do you think, Big Sis Sara?
That's a pretty out-there idea.
I'm pretty sure ghosts don't exist.
But I saw it.
Last night, when I was walking down the hallway...
How unlucky...
Then, I met a terrible fate.
And that's why you're sticking to me
like glue, Miss Erna?
Because you're afraid of the ghost?
If you're scared, you're welcome to come on in.
Your animals are scary too.
There's a ghost in the manor,
and there are your animals in the shed.
I'm stuck between a rock and a hard place.
Don't be silly.
My pets wouldn't hurt a fly.
He won't bite me?
I've trained him not to.
You can borrow him to use as a guard dog
to protect you from the ghost.
He's super toasty when he sleeps with you at night.
A-and you're sure he doesn't bite?
Positive, I made sure to teach him that it's not okay to-
No, no, he's just play-biting.
It's a way of showing affection, so it shouldn't hurt.
...Does it hurt?
YEEEEEEEP!
I'm so, so sorry!
I feel so guilty about what happened back there.
Plus, I'm pretty sure that ghost she saw was-
Who could be up this late?
All the others are asleep
because of how tired they are from training.
B-but in that case...
is it a burglar?
Is that you, Sara?
T-Teach?!
Wh-what are you doing?
It's as you can see.
You mean you're washing dishes?
What, is it really that odd to see me doing housework?
A-a little bit, yeah.
This is part of my training.
There are times when I need to
masquerade as a butler or a chef.
Also, I was the lowest in
the pecking order on my old team.
Doing the chores got to be a habit.
People have many sides to them.
And you're no different.
That toolbox you're carrying.
You're the one who's been repairing the manor
night after night, aren't you?
Magnificent.
You didn't like the situation,
so you decided to work alone
to support your teammates.
I commend your altruism.
Not many people would have done that,
much less chosen to
remain anonymous while doing so.
However, I'm less pleased with the fact that
you're the only one losing sleep over this.
If the manor's state is getting in the way of your training,
then you really ought to be repairing it as a group.
I'll let the others know tomorrow.
I'm sorry you've had to handle all the repairs yourself.
No, not it at all!
You, um, you don't have to tell the others
about what I've been doing.
Why's that?
I recognize that I'm the weakest member on the team.
I spent the least amount of time attending
a spy academy out of everyone here.
Though even if we'd gone for
the same amount of time,
I probably would still have fallen behind.
The point is, I know I'm not a very good spy.
The least I can do is help out so the others
can get a good night's sleep.
This is me recognizing my place,
just like my academy taught me to.
What the hell kind of education
are they giving over there?
You should head to bed for the night, Sara.
I read you loud and clear.
Y-yes, sir.
Please, Miss Lily, you have to get up!
We're in charge of making breakfast, remember?
C'mon, leave me alone.
I didn't steal the cookies, I swear.
What is she dreaming about?
Sure, I went over to the cupboard.
But all I did was move them a teensy bit.
Where to?
My tummy.
That's clearly stealing them!
I just had a horrible nightmare
where I was falsely accused of stuff.
That's just obviously a lie.
Now, we need to hurry or the others will wake up.
Huh? What's that nice smell?
Good morning, Sara and Lily.
Teach? What's going on?
I thought it might be nice for me
to treat you to a meal every now and then.
Could you go wake the others up?
Hot damn, that was tasty.
That was exquisite.
I'm so glad you're our boss, Bro!
I'll follow you to the ends of the Earth.
If I was ever gonna find someone
better at cooking than me,
it makes sense it'd be you.
I'd be happy to date you,
if it meant getting to eat like this every day.
As your superior, rewarding you for
your efforts is part of the job.
This dressing...
is especially delicious!
It's really something else!
It's plenty tasty on its own,
but when boiled down with pepper and red wine,
it becomes a wonderful steak sauce.
And I just so happened to pick up some
fresh beef tenderloin at the market this morning.
I'm letting it breathe for a bit,
but by tonight, it will be perfect.
He doesn't miss, yo!
He's the perfect boss!
He's the self-proclaimed World's Strongest!
Teach! Teach! Teach! Teach!
I had no idea you all would be so pleased.
I'm happy you feel that way.
Teach! Teach! Teach! Teach!
But I have to ask,
who said that any of you were getting this meat?
Teach! Teach! Teach! Teach-
Um, what happened to rewarding your subordinates?
I made you breakfast, didn't I?
What about the tenderloin you just bought?
That's for my dinner.
You got anything you want to say to us?
Hurry up and get back to your training.
Meat! Meat!
Meat! Meat! Meat! Meat!
If you want this steak,
what do you say we have a little contest?
A what?
Don't worry.
I'm not a monster.
The odds will be overwhelmingly in your favor.
FILE: Meadow Sara
The rules of the contest are simple.
We'll be competing to see who can mend the door,
clean the bath, sweep the hall, replace a window,
and wipe the other windows the fastest.
Those will be our five rounds,
and if you beat in me in any of them,
the steak is yours.
However, using violence to obstruct
the other team is against the rules.
Got it?
Bring it on!
Meat! Meat!
The first round will be mending the door.
Whichever side returns their door to
its original state first is the winner.
What exactly is that?
It's a starting bell I made!
Can you rig it so that Teach ends up
starting after we do?
That doesn't make any sense, yo.
The key will be figuring out how to
leverage our numbers to our advantage.
If we can figure out a way to use all
seven of us at the same time...
Worry not, with me at the helm, this will be a breeze.
It's time for me show just what I'm made of.
Is everyone ready?
Sybilla, go measure the damaged section!
Monika and Lily,
you're in charge of cutting the wood!
Sara, prep the varnish and paint
we're going to use for the-
All done.
B-but how?
Once I jammed my knife in,
cut the wood with suitable movements,
and accurately eyeballed the measurements,
all I had to do was be as fast as
a winter wind descending a mountain.
What do you mean,
"accurately eyeballed the measurements"?
So, we lost?
It would seem that way.
So, we're cleanin' the bath for round two?
We brought too many people
on the mission last time.
We're gonna change up the plan a bit for this one.
How so?
We'll dedicate one person to getting in Klaus's way,
and I'll pull out at all the stops
to make up the difference.
Well, this is a change.
I never thought I'd hear you
get so serious about something.
You want the meat that bad?
Oh, shut up.
I'm just sick of losing all the time.
But isn't running interference against the rules?
Physical attacks are a no-go, sure.
Lily, duty calls.
Aye aye, cap'n!
If you need someone harassed, I'm your gal!
She's enjoying herself a bit too much.
Heya, Teach.
I've been meaning to ask,
but do you have any friends?
You totally don't, do you?
You want me to hang out with you?
All you gotta do is pay!
What's that, cat got your tongue?
Are you pretending to be focusing on your cleaning
so you can cry on the inside?
By the way, Lily...
What are you planning on doing after you beat me?
Sure, you'll get your hands on some steak.
But it will be split into sevenths,
and only one of them will be yours.
If you join my side, though,
you could get the whole steak to yourself.
Did that thought ever cross your mind?
You're a clever girl.
I'm sure you'll make the right call.
I'm sorry, everyone!
The showerhead started spraying you all on its own!
You rat! How many times must you sabotage me
before you've had your fill?!
I-I'll never give in to your torture!
I'm all done cleaning.
And Lily, I was lying earlier.
You traitor!
You don't get to use that word!
It looks like we can't rely on the others for this.
I had no idea they were so useless.
I'm disappointed in them, yo.
Oh, the two of them sound fired up!
Do you have some sort of plan?
I smell misfortune.
Oh, all her dust blew over to a spot
Teach just finished sweeping!
That's going to cost him a lot of time!
I've got your back, yo.
Time to break out my
special deluxe cleaning machine!
Yeeeeeeep!
I'm all done sweeping.
Pretty sure we would've won
if you hadn't gotten in my way, yo.
That was clearly all your fault!
I'll handle this one solo.
That will give me more room to move,
so I'll be able to use my full strength.
You all can just shut up and watch me.
All done.
How?!
Good going, Boss!
Hey, whose side are you on?!
Here it is, the final round.
The last round is a window washing showdown.
Whoever cleans their set of second-floor
windows first wins the whole thing.
Our numbers advantage should
give us a massive edge...
...but I still don't see us winning.
Water's gonna be the bottleneck here, huh?
Water?
The quickest way to wash is by making
a huge splash all over the window,
then wiping it clean in one big go.
The problem is, it'll take too long
to come down for more water
and get back up to the second floor
between each window.
It's more of a hassle, but our only real choice
is to spray them a little at a time
so we can get them wet while
still conserving our water.
Wait, but...
If we just need to transport water...
Sara?!
Forget her!
Every second counts here!
Found them!
I'm code name Meadow,
and it's time to run circles around them!
Damn, Teach is already two-thirds of the way done!
But we only just got to the halfway point!
I'll never throw in the towel!
Meat! Meat!
Everyone!
I've got something for you!
Mr. Bernard!
Mr. Aiden!
This might do the trick!
We've got this!
Mr. Johnny!
We're making good time!
We're right on his heels, yo!
Yeep!
I'm just getting started!
Meat...
In the end, he swept us 5-0.
Eh, could've been worse.
At least he cooked us that one pity steak.
But we had to split it seven ways!
I finished mine in a single bite!
Anyways, I'm gonna turn in.
I'm beat.
A-actually, if I may.
Would it be all right if I made a suggestion?
What do you say to starting up
a repairs rotation after all?
I think it would be for the best.
Like I said yesterday, I object.
You really think we've got time for that
when we've got a life-or-death mission
just two weeks away?
But doing repairs is a form of training too.
Being a spy isn't only about taking down targets.
Having to deal with the cooking and cleaning
is enough of a hassle already.
But Miss Monika, don't you play hooky
from those all the time?
Oh dear, that's not a very good look.
Dang, she's really got you there.
I respect your strength a lot, Miss Monika.
But chores are chores.
We need to be fair about how we split them up.
...Is kind of sort of how I feel.
B-but I'm probably speaking out of turn, aren't I?
I fully agree.
Fine, I'll do better.
Good, so you were able to broach
the topic with the others.
I was!
And it's all thanks to you, Teach.
Thank you so much.
I'm sure I don't know what you're talking about.
Are you sure about this, though?
This is really fancy meat.
You and your little ones were today's MVPs.
Do you come here often, Teach?
They seem used to you.
Wait, could the ghost that Miss Erna
saw around here have actually been...
I'm a big animal lover.
That's kind of surprising.
Back when we first met, I got the impression
you were kind of a cold person.
People have many sides to them.
You shouldn't worry about how they evaluated you
back at your academy, Sara.
All they saw was a single one of your sides.
There will be plenty of days where you shine,
just like you did today.
There's no need for you
to recognize any sort of place.
Yes, sir!
Magnificent.
This little guy is especially cute.
That's Mr. Johnny.
He had this bad habit of biting everything
in sight back when he was first born,
but lately, he hasn't bitten anyone-
Except for that one time.
He bit someone?
He gnawed on Miss Erna's hand a bit.
That seems in-character for her.
I should be fine, though.
I'm an expert at dealing with-
I-I'm so, so-
There's nothing to apologize for.
He's just showing his affection.
I'm not so sure about that...
You really think I would screw up like that?
Oh, no, of course not,
but are you sure you're not just
putting on a strong face?
Perish... the thought.
You're clearly fighting through the pain, sir.
Not at all.
It doesn't hurt... one bit.
The odd pauses aren't helping your case!
I'm just an inexperienced spy who hasn't even
properly trained Mr. Johnny yet,
but I hope that someday,
I'll get a chance to do big things.
In fact, I'm sure I will!
Boss,
the nine of us are a new team called Lamplight,
and we're going to pick up where Inferno left off.
I hope you're watching over us.
Congratulations.
In light of it having successfully retrieved Abyss Doll,
Lamplight has been formally promoted
to an official team.
How are the girls?
They got ten days off as part of their reward
for completing the mission,
so they're probably all off on vacation right now.
Well, that's fine.
The reason I called you here today
is because we have a lead
on that mysterious sniper who killed Guido.
We don't know how large it is,
and despite pursuing them for years,
we don't have any solid intel on them.
But the Empire's top spy team is called Serpent,
and that sniper was likely one of its members.
Serpent...